[{"answer": "Well, first of all, it's very dangerous to try to preventively detain people based on predictions of what they're liking to do in the future.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "What can we do about it?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "I think that's exactly right.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "Because as there are more of them, the need to do something becomes more and more urgent, doesn't it?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "A ROAD TRIP\": The first thing you do is you do no harm.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 72, "question": "Dan Baum, how do you make it harder for crazy people to legally buy weapons that they can go and do crazy things with?", "qSentId": 71}, {"answer": "Well, of course it doesn't mean what you just said.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 132, "question": "What do you do about that culture?", "qSentId": 131}, {"answer": "Well, I mean -- let me just -- before we go to Alan, what I would say is, it's very good to have the debate.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 214, "question": "Can I respond to that?", "qSentId": 213}, {"answer": "Well, homicide, murder, is a byproduct of many different qualities.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 281, "question": "But this particular one of crazy people doing crazy things, what can you do to try and red flag these people?", "qSentId": 280}, {"answer": "Well, two things.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 322, "question": "What do we do about that?", "qSentId": 321}, {"answer": "Mass shooting is an end point in an individual who may have mental illness and who may not.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Unless it is to do harm?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I don't agree.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "Final question, though, I mean, from all that you have seen, all the cases you've been involved in, and so on, do you think there is a coherent argument to just have tougher gun laws in America?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "Well, it's actual fact.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "Why are you going all out then against President Obama over this?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "Well, there's nothing wrong with flexibility.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 405, "question": "Would you go along with that?", "qSentId": 404}, {"answer": "Governor Romney in this letter would have undermined the work requirement.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 416, "question": "Ben Labolt?", "qSentId": 415}, {"answer": "I think I'd have to agree with Governor Romney when he called that Obama-loney.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 443, "question": "It's got a certain ring to it, hasn't it?", "qSentId": 442}, {"answer": "Well, people ask me if I knew it was a shark.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 503, "question": "When a Great White Shark sinks its fangs into you, what does it feel like?", "qSentId": 502}, {"answer": "I think the most surprising thing to me about this whole incident is that I didn't actually feel afraid.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 520, "question": "Why did you stay so cool?", "qSentId": 519}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "It's harder for me to know what was going through his mind.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 538, "question": "Was your son as phlegmatic about it all as you clearly were?", "qSentId": 537}, {"answer": "No, no, no, no.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 548, "question": "No, you wouldn't stick around to chat, would you?", "qSentId": 547}, {"answer": "People's fear of shark attacks -- and I spoke to a couple of folks today, and they said God, I would never get in the water.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "Or is it simply that with the modern media phenomena, that when there is an attack like this, it gets such a huge play on the Twitter-verse, if you like, that it seems like there are a lot more?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "We speculate that that's the case.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "And if that is true, why do they keep gnawing it at?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Chris, you say you were swimming back with your son.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 603, "question": "Why not?", "qSentId": 602}, {"answer": "Euphoria.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 605, "question": "When you actually got back to land, what was your reaction then?", "qSentId": 604}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 608, "question": "Did you realize then the enormity of what you just survived?", "qSentId": 607}, {"answer": "I'm walking around.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 629, "question": "How is your leg?", "qSentId": 628}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 652, "question": "Is winning an Olympic gold for you the absolute number one dream?", "qSentId": 651}, {"answer": "Yeah, definitely, especially in the car ride to and from gym.", "docId": "120807pmt", "aSentId": 660, "question": "For all seven hours of the day, you're think of that gold medal, the podium, the American anthem?", "qSentId": 659}]